Guide to the Lincoln Steffens Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III. Letters of Lincoln Steffens
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1913 June 30, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 July 6, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 July 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1913 July 21, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1913 July 30, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 July 31, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1913 August 1, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 August 1, (a.l.s.,4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Marie Howe, 1913 August 4, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Marie Howe, 1913 August 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 August 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 August 8, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Marie Howe, 1913 August 10, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1913 August 8, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 September 8, (a.l.s.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 September 15, (a.l.s., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1913 September 19, (a.l.s., 7p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 September 20, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 September 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Marie Howe, 1913 October 1, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 October 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 October 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 November 1, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), Allen H. Suggett, Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), and John James Hollister, 1913 November 16, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1913 November 1, (a.l.s, 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 November 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 December 8, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 December 10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 66)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1913 December 19, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1913 December 20, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1913 December 24, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1913 December 24, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 66)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 January 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 January 19, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1914 January 19, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 January 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 February 9, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), and Allen H. Suggett, 1914 February 10, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1914 February 12, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 February 26, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 March 2, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 March 8, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1914 March 22, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 March 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 April 4, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 April 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 April 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 April 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1914 April 16, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 April 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1914 April 25, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 April 27, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 May 5, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 May 9, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 May 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 May 31, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 June 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 June 6, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 June 17, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 June 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 September 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 September 30, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 October 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 October 9, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 67)
  - Suggett, Lou Steffens (Second Mrs. Allen H.). To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 October 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 October 10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 October 28, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
  - Hollister, John James? To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1914 October 28, (a.l.s., 1p., at bottom of above letter) (Box 67)
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 October 28, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1914 November 4, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 November 4, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 November 5, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 November 14, (a.l.s., 2p., First two pages of longer letter.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 November 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 November 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 November 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 November 23, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1914 December 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 January 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 January 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 January 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Jack Hollister, 1915 January 31, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1915 February 12, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1915 February 24, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1915 March 5, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 March 10, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 March 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 March 31, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1915 March 31, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 April 7, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 April 25, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 May 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 June 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 June 17, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 June 28, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 July 8, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 67)
    - To Clinton Hollister, 1915 July 12, (a.l.s.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 August 6, (a.l.s.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 September 9, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 September 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 September 15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1915 September 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1915 September 17, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 September 23, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1915 October 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1915 October 3, (a.l.s., 8p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 October 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 October 14, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 October 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1915 October 17, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 October 20, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 October 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 November 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 November 17, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1915 December 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 December 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1915 December 15, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 67)
  - Suggett, Allen H. and Lou Steffens. To Lincoln Steffens, 1915 March 1-4, (a. and t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 January 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 January 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 January 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 January 27, (a.l.s.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 February 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 February 2, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 February 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 March 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1916 March 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 March 24, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 April 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 April 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 April 9, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 April 12, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 April 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 April 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 April 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 May 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 May 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1916 May 16, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 May 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 May 31, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 June 2, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 June 5, (a.l.s., 11p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 June 9, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 June 12, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 June 12, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 June 17, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 June 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 June 19, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, circa 1916 July, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 July 1, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 July 1, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 July 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 July 4, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 July 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1916 July 16, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 July 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 July 22, (a.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 July 25, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 July 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 August 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 August 2, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 67)
  - Older, Fremont, 1916 July 25, (t.l.s., 1p., with above letter) (Box 67)
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 August 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 August 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 August 6, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To John James Hollister, 1916 September 8, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 September 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 September 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 September 29, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 October 5, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 October 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 October 18, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 October 23, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 October 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 October 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 October 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 November 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 December 12, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 December 19, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 67)
    - To John James Hollister, 1916 December 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1916 December 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 December 28, (a.l.s.) (Box 67)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1916 December 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1916 December 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 67)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1917 January 9, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 January 10, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope and additional note in an unidentified hand) (Box 68)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 January 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 January 12, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1917 January 20, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 January 22, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 February 5, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1917 February 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 February 11, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope and related letter from Clinton Hollister to Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James)) (Box 68)
    - To Lou Steffens Suggett (1st Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 February 15, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 March 3, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 March 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 March 18, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 March 20, (a.l.s.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 March 22, (a.l.s., 2p.,with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 March 24, (telegram.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 March 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 March 27, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 April 1, (telegram, with related telegram) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 April 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 April 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 May 29, (a.p.c.s.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 May 30, (a.p.c.s.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 June 14, (telegram, with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 June 14, (a.l.s.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 June 16, (a.l.s., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 June 19, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1917 June 20, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 June 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 June 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 June 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 July 6, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 July 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 September 15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 September 16, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 September 16, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 September 26, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 September 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1917 September 30, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1917 October 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 October 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 October 6, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 October 11, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 October 20, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1917 October 23, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1917 October 24, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 October 25, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1917 October 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1917 October 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 November 1, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 November 6, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1917 November 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 November 17, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 November 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 December 10, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 December 17, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1917 December 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 December 21, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1917 December 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1917 December 27, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1917 December 30, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 January 5, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 January 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 January 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 January 31, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 February 6, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 February 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 February 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 February 13, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 February 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 February 18, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 February 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 February 26, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 March 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 March 10, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1918 March 11, (a.l.s., 3p, with related item.) (Box 68)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1918 March 12, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 March 14, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 68)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1918 March 16, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 68)